Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Meeting Records SC1010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records created prior to 2010, 1885-2009; Series 1
  - Supporting material, 1905-1976, 1998-2009; Subseries 3; 28 Linear Feet (56 boxes)
    - Pension Plan; Budget; Scholarships and gifts., 1921 Jan 28 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Government grant; Northern Electric securities; Stanford Union construction; Food Research Institute - Carnegie Corporation of New York agreement; Faculty Housing Fund - lease resolution; Pacific Improvement Co. - land sale to U. C; Seattle land - sold; Resolution that the Univ. not enter into an expansive building program; Scholarships; Oil painting, A. W. Hoisholt given to Medical School., 1921 Feb 25 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Pacific Improvement Co; T. W. Stanford Estate; Union Trust Co; Copy of property lease., 1921 Mar 25 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Tuition for graduate students, law and medical students; L. H. Sly: proposal to use Stanford Court Apts. to endow a chair of Biblical Study and Research; Study: Whether or not trust funds can be used for the erection of buildings for education plant purposes if they do or do not produce income; Commonwealth Fund gift for a study of gifted children by Terman; 1920 Senior Class Endowment Fund., 1921 Apr 29 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Edmund Cogswell Converse bequest., 1921 May 5 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Scholarship Awards; Leave of absence report; U. S. Social Hygiene Board grant; Hopkins Marine Station - purchase of acreage from Del Monte properties; Stadium contract; C. A. Canfield bequest., 1921 May 27 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - David Hewes gift to hospital; Deans appointed; Medical faculty - articles of organization; President's salary raised; Plans for financing hotel on campus submitted by City of Palo Alto; Civil Engineering Scholarships., 1921 Jun 24 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Wylie M. Giffen - loan; Palo Alto tree; Entler property report; Lane Medical Library - gift for Dr. Adolph Barken., 1921 Aug 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Student Guild - proposal that it be taken over by the University; Victoria Morris Smith - plans for hotel on campus; Mayfield - street paving; T. W. Stanford Estate; Aronson Loan., 1921 Aug 26 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - School of Nursing; Howard - campus land lease; Endowment Comm. - Fund raising campaign - 3 million; Mrs. George Hemple - widow's pension; French Republic Gold Bonds; Endowment Fund - Class of 1921; Hotel Site - Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce., 1921 Oct 4 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Copy of faculty lease; T. W. Stanford Estate., 1921 Oct 28 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Basketball pavillion; Lane Library - gift: Dr. Adolph Barkan; General Education Board - payment increase teachers salaries., 1921 Nov 25 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - U. S. Liberty Bonds bought; Standard Oil of N. J. stock; Max Farrand, Commonwealth Fund - grant for the study of gifted children, 1922 Jan 12 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Football coach - salary (7500 plus 2500 allowance.); Gifts., 1922 Jan 27 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Latin and Greek Depts. combined to form Classics; School of Biology., 1922 Feb 24 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - J. C. Branner - death; Endowment Comm. - Fundraising plans; Japanese Assoc. of America - grant for a Terman study of Japanese school children in Calif., 1922 Mar 31 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Campus Comm. - hotels, streets, dorms, etc.; Hotel discussion; J. C. Branner - memorial resolution; General Education Board - grant., 1922 Apr 28 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Oakland Water Front property; Heads of Departments named; Bailey Willis retirement; Purchase and sale of stocks and bonds; Report to National Canners Associaton on the botulism study; First Million fund., 1922 May 12 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Stanford School of Nursing, agreement between U.C., S.F. Hospital School of Nursing and Stanford; Deed for Palo Alto given to Trustee of Stanford by Timothy Hopkins - to uphold liquor ruling; Gifts; Board of Athletic Control offer to build dorm., 1922 Jun 30 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Terms of lease of land by S. U. for hotel purposes., 1922 Jul 5 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - World War I memorial - one of the milestones marking battle line of the Allies, 1918; Mayfield land lease; Encina dining hall and new dorm costs; Fountain for Memorial Court - Class of 1922; Gifts, to Hoover War Library - $53,483.34., 1922 Aug 1 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Endowment Campaign; T. W. Stanford estate; Commision for Relief in Belgium - contracts for preserving records of C. R. B; Gifts., 1922 Sep 29 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Searsville Lake property; Grammar school site corner of Stanford Avenue; Comm. for Relief in Belgium trust fund., 1922 Oct 27 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - F. B. Anderson reelected Trustee., 1922 Nov 2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - C. R. B; San Francisco property adjoining hospital offered to S. U. for purchase., 1922 Nov 24 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Herbert Hoover re-elected trustee; W. May Newell reelected trustee., 1922 Dec 14 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Ephraim and Amelia Weiss give Berkeley property jointly to Stanford and U. C., 1922 Dec 26 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Treasurer's estimate of income; Hoover's gift to War Library - $58,000., 1923 Jan 26 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Gifts., 1923 Feb 15 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - C. D. Marx retirement; Wm Roberts Eckart Research Fund and gifts of tools, etc.; Vina Land sale; South Yuba Water Company; Vina Ranch Lands; Mayfield school property list; Carnegie Institution grant to study silkworms; David Starr Jordan - gift to Hoover War Library, books on War and Peace., 1923 Mar 30 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Wm. B. Bourn - resignation as Trustee; Convalescent Home., 1923 Apr 19 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Women's Club - fees for graduate women; General Education Board - grant for teacher's salaries; Food Research Institute - grant from Carnegie Corporation; Robert M. Loeser Print Collection - gift; Cebrian gift of Spanish books., 1923 Apr 27 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Executive heads of Depts. named; Academic Committees of the Faculty named; Dr. W. L. Holman resignation; New House for Jordans; Samuel F. Leib resignation as Trustee; Charles P. Eels resignation as Trustee; Branner Memorial Assoc; Masonic Club request for a building on campus. - turmed down; E. W. Hopkins Scholarship fund; Charles A. Huston Memorial Book Fund., 1923 Jun 1 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Stanford National Board - members., 1923 Jun 29 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - C. O. G. Miller elected to board of trustees; Ira S. Lillick elected to board of trustees; Harry F. Chandler elected to board of trustees; Nominations for trustees; Budget; Sale of land at Ione; T. W. Stanford fund., 1923 Aug 14 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Stanford Home for Convalescent Children; American Relief Administration trust fund to Hoover War Library - $250,000., 1923 Sep 28 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Bussey-Webb Memorial Lectureship - bequest; Branner Memorial Assoc; Gift of books to Imperial Univ. of Tokyo after their library was destroyed; Orrin W. Dunn Scholarship; Benno Loewy estate; Plan for greater diversification of investments through the conversion of railroad securities; Concerning tenure and members of Board of Trustees; Stanford War Memorial; National Board - declining letters; Munchi Van Wolbeck gift to herbarium; Herbert Hoover's gift of books on geology., 1923 Oct 26 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Paul Shoup elected Trustee; American Relief Administration trust fund., 1923 Dec 11 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Tatlock collection of books collected in preparation of Chaucer Concordance - gift; American Relief Administration; Ryan High Voltage Laboratory; Sebrian gift of 33 Spanish books; Col. John Howard - gift of books on Military Training; Commonwealth Fund grant for study of "The Structure of the Intellect."; National Research Council grant for study of the sex habits of rats., 1923 Dec 28 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - School of Social Sciences; Mrs. Stillman's widow's pension; Jordan letter of thanks for new house; Carnegie Corporation grant to Food Research Institute; Judge E. M. Wilson gift of equipment to Dept. of Mining and Metallurgy; H. R. Montalban - gift of fishes; F. H. Seares - gift of Clarence T. Urmy Library; Timothy Hopkins gift of letters and documents of Mark Hopkins, C. P. Huntington, Leland Stanford, of the late 60's and early 70's relating to the early railroad history, 1924 Jan 25 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Title, Director of the University Libraries, instituted; School of Social Sciences formed; Admission requirements; Wm. F. Durand, Wm. H. Carruth retire; College of Electronic Medicine Consolidation proposed; Hoover War Library; Vina Ranch Land sale; Robert Patek Memorial Loan Fund; Stanford Women's Club of San Francisco Scholarship, 1924 Feb 21 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Adolph Barkan gift to Lane Medical Library; Admissions requirements; National Electric light Assoc. Scholarship; B.P.O.E. Scholarship; College of Electronic Medicine - consolidation proposal; Ella B. Briggs bequest; Business Courses set up in cooperation with Retail Merchants Assoc; Emmet Rixford Scholarship in Surgery; Gifts, 1924 Mar 28 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Fellowships established; Commendation to Prof. Gilbert from Assoc. of Pacific Fisheries; Fee for Nurses Training School; Stillman library gift; Dr. Chas. Rees Harry gift to Lane Library; General Education Board raise of teachers salaries; Carnegie Corporation grant to Food Research Institute; Labor and Mueller Collection of lepidopter - gift, 1924 Apr 25 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Issuance of tuition scrip to the teachers who supervised practice teachers for Stanford; Law School admission policy; Campus and Grounds Comm. report - landscaping; Stanford Home for Convalescent Children - Stanford Trustees refuse trusteeship of; J. C. Cebrian - gift of collection of Spanish periodicals; 1911 Juris Doctor Class - gift to Law Library; W. F. George - gift of husband's law library; Marvin A. Ives - gift of 69 letters and documents of Butler Ives - an engineer of the C.P.R.R., 1924 Jun 27 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Medical School expansion plans; Stanford Convalescent Home (new name); First Million endowment; Grad. School of Business Comm; National Academy of Sciences award to Henry H. Henline; National Canners Assoc. grant for botulism study; Carnegie Corp. grant to F.R.I; Pacific Oil Co. grant for petroleum research; Siamese Embassy - gift of Buddhist Scripture; Comm. for Research on Sex Problems of the National Research Council; Selah Chamberlain resignation from Board of Trustees, 1924 Aug 8 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Hoover War Library - $5000 given from S.U. funds for purchase of books; Dr. Wallace H. Barnes death; Wm Roberts Eckart Prize - Mechanical Engineering; Endowment Secretary - proposed; Publication of L. M. Terman's study of gifted children; General Education Board's grant to increase teachers' salaries; Vina Sheep ranch; Jackson H. Ralston gift of 113 books to Library; Wm. S. Cranston Memorial Scholarship, 1924 Sep 26 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Academic Council membership opened to members of staffs of library and administration; Raymond Macdonald Alder death; Charles Wooster - retirement pension, came west with Sen. Stanford in 1869; Post Office lease; Hotel proposed; Branner house - Mrs. Branner wanted to will it to her son; Carnegie Corporation grant to F. R. I; David Belasco - Shakespeare manuscripts; Wellington Greegg fund; Roy N. Bishop, W. R. Eckart, Cyrus Clay Carpenter, Jr. books - former Governor of Iowa; Margaret Sidney Scholarship - give by Miss Margaret Lathrop; Gifts; Wallace M. Alexander elected trustee, 1924 Oct 31 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Mayfield land lease; Mechanical Engineering Dept. - prizes; Commonwealth Fund - study of Foster children, 1924 Dec 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Timothy Hopkins - gift of rare books; Mayfield property purchase; Gifts, 1924 Dec 30 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - William Herbert Carruth - memorial resolution; Judge Samuel F. Leib - memorial resolution; Ephraim Weiss - loan; Hempl lease questioned; Joseph and Georgia Reed Fife - Scholarship fund; Herbert C. Jones, gift to law library, 1925 Jan 30 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - R. L. Rigdon - retirement; Prof. Bruno Boezinger - extension of retirement age; Prof. E. W. Schulty - loan; J. E. Coover - loan; Roy H. Button - loan; Blanket insurance proposal - and plant appraisal; Charles W. Willard scholarship for advanced work in nursing; Canegie Corporation grant for study of adult education; H. H. Judah gift to Hopkins Railway Library; Nellie B. Hammond Fund; Joan Howell memorial fund to medical school; Adolph Barkan gift to medical library; J. C. Cebrian gift to library of Spanish books, 1925 Mar 27 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Lane Library periodical fund; Palo Alto property lease and loan; Wm. F. Herrin Scholarship fund; H. C. Dudley gift for maintenance of Dudley Herbarium; East Bay Stanford Women's Club Loan Fund; Stanford Chapter of the American Society of Civil Engineering Scholarship, 1925 Apr 17 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Divisionof Public Speaking to be autonomous; Carnegie Pension rules; Report on Engineering School, Curricula and Degrees by the President's Comm. of Seven; Increase in Univ. Fellowships; Hopkins Marine Station budget increase; Trustee meeting rules; Timothy Hopkins - gift of framed engravings, 1925 May 16 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Directors of Hoover War Library named; Rockefeller Foundation grant to Hopkins Marine Station; Stanford Graduate School of Business established; Willard E. Hotchkiss appointed dean of G.S. of B; D. H. Campbell Fund; Building alterations; Gift ot Dept. of Electrical Engineering and High Voltage Lab; Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Fund; Gifts and Grants; Loans for construction of residences on campus, 1925 Jun 18 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Independent study plan; Additional Blanket Insurance proposal; Modification of resolution and accounting treatment of amortization of losses on bond transactions; Am. Smelting and Refining Company Scholarship; Gift to Ryan lab; Gifts, bequests, and scholarships, 1925 Aug 13 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Student Guild Hospital Comm. - services and fees; Land leases and loans; Adolph Barkan - oil painting (copy of Pompeii original) donated to Lane Library; Dr. Paolo de Vecchi - gift of Italian books; Mrs. M. H. Heynemann - gift of autographed portrait of Thomas Paine; Carnegie Corporation grant to F. R. I; Florence Hecht Fries Scholarship in Medicine, 1925 Oct 8 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Board of Athletic Control annual appropriation for the support of Physical Education dept; Class of 1928 payment for damage to Encina in student rioting; Revision of the General requirements for admission; Resolution on Academic Freedom and Tenure adopted by the Association of American Colleges; Palo Alto Theatre Company request that liquor restriction clause by waived, 1925 Dec 10 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Restroom on Quad; Medical School; Hetch Hetchy High Voltage Transmission lines - not allowed to cross University property, 1926 Jan 14 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - [none listed], 1926 Feb 11 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - [none listed], 1926 Mar 18 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Masters of Business Administration degree; Comm. on Graduate Study - fees; Engineering degree: A. B. or B. S., 1926 Apr 8 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Elizabeth Waters Burbank: offered Stanford the Luther Burbak experimental farm with everything included for $50,000; Law Library - stack equipment; Prudential Insurance co. granted waiver of liquor restriction, 1926 May 13 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - School of Letters proposed; School Physical Sciences established; Rockefeller grant to Hopkins Marine Station, building to be named Jacque Loeb Laboratory for Marine Physiology; Menlo Park - Stanford boundary land purchased by Stanford; Pradere Range rental; Class of ‘99 gift to endowment fund, 1926 Jun 14 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Articles of Organization of Academic Council - eligible members; Modification of University regulations regarding graduate standing, fees, etc.; University fee policy; Power of Trustees to invest funds of the University in stocks, 1926 Jul 8 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Comptrollers report; Gifts, Aug 12, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Construction of bridge over San Francisquito Creek; Purchase of property adjoining Stanford hospital; Purchase of Searsville Lake Property; Durham Ranch - extension given for payment; Woodside Country Club - lease of Searsville Lake property; Comm. to investigate status of Trust and State law relative to investment in preferred stock, and to recommend practical procedure - report; Increased annuity for T. W. Stanford's housekeeper; Purchase of Schroder picnic ground, 1926 Sep 16 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Letter from Mrs. Luther Burbank offering to include the house with the Santa Rosa farm; Re establishing a department of music; City of Palo Alto reservoir; Tennis court adjoining Nurses' dorm; Comptroller - list of leases; Audubon prints presented, 1926 Oct 14 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Grank P. Deering elected Trustee, 1926 Nov 16 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Gifts, 1926 Nov 16 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Gifts, 1926 Dec 9 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Gifts to Bender Room; Other gifts, 1927 Jan 13 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Fund for tuition scholarships; Medical School fees raised; Wilbur's recommendation that Stanford lease land for the Santa Clara County Junior College; Charles B. Turrill collection of documents, books, and photos bought; Board of Athletic Control - stadium subscriptions given for endowments; Gifts, Scholarships, etc., 1927 Feb 10 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Gifts, 1927 Mar 10 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - E. P. cubberley request for a new educational building, including therein his suggestions for its site, plans, and the financing of it; Requirements for Law degree; Revised plan of organization of the School of Education; Further limitations of the Lower Division; Insurance for S. F. medical school buildings; Geology Dept. - purchase of a truck; Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial grant for program in Social Sciences; W. B. Bourn - gift of Vallejo-Bosqui Turrill vol. of Zamorano Imprints, 1927 Apr 14 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Dept. of Psychology included in the School of Social Sciences; Dr. G. Alfred Lawrence - bequest "Nuggets Fund" to collect Stanfordiana, 1927 May 12 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Leases; Gifts; Appointments, 1927 Jun 9 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Purchase of San Francisco Land, 1927 Jul 14 (Box 17, Folder 14.5)
    - Changes in Articles of Organization; Agreement between S. U., Calif., and the U.S.S.R. to carry on the work of the Russiona Revolution Institute; Gold Spike deposited in Union Trust Co; Purchase of S. F. land; Gifts, 1927 Aug 11 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Re establishing a college of dentistry; Gifts, bequests, 1927 Oct 13 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Branner Seismometer Station ready to operate; Gas Lines bought (sought?) by City of Palo Alto; Menlo School and Junior College wants to lease Cedro Cottage for a proposed Junior College; Plans for a flying field, 1927 Nov 17 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - General Education Board - $750,000 for general endowment of Stanford University; E. Ed. degree established, 1927 Dec 8 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Proposed flying school; Gifts, Jan 5, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Sale of water blocks in Alameda Co; Restrictions on leases of campus land, Mar 15, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Establishment of Ed.D. degree; Druham Land Colony - State project which failed; Recommendation that the Searsville dam be inspected, Apr 12, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Trust established for Jennie Lawton and her children by Mrs. Stanford, 1928 May 10 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Kate Felton Neilson bequest of Charlotte Ashley Felton Room; Gifts to Hoover War Library; Sale of the last of Mrs. Stanford's jewels; three brown pearls; Loans to fraternitieis for house improvements, 1928 Jul 19 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Patience Wells Kimball: claim on the estate of Mark Hopkins; Addition to Stanford Hospital proposed, Aug 13, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Hospital facilities for Univ. community of Palo Alto, Sep 25, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Plan for co-operation between Hopkins Marine Station and the California Fish and Game Commission; Proposal to make a museum out of the old winery; University Club - land purchase, Oct 11, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - List of degrees granted; Scholarship awards; Various property matters (in San Francisco and on campus); Gifts and bequests, Dec 13, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Alexander Agassiz Laboratory" suggested as name for Hopkins marine Station building, Jan. 10, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Pension report; Board of Athletic Control granted a lease for a golf course; Stanford hospital addition (in S. F.); Financial Comm. report on use of Trust; Robert U. Frick elected Trustee, Feb. 14, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Felt Lake: plans to increase it, Mar. 14, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Timothy Hopkins: re memoralizing Mr. Stanford's love of horses; contributions to horse raising, motion pictures - a park around the barn; Re Charlotte Askley Felton Library, 1929 May 16 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Board of Athletic Control plans for a women's gymnasium, 1929 Jun 13 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Gifts, 1929 Jul 23 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Gifts, Aug. 14, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - T. T. C. Gregory reelected Trustee; First Million Campaign; Increase in tuition fees - no action, Sept. 12, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Dr. R. E. Swain acting president; Carnegie Corporation of N. Y. grant to study education and occupational opportunities for American citizen of Oriental races, Oct. 10, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Pacific Botanic Foundation - proposed by Emory E. Smith; List of degrees granted; George J. Presley elected Trustee; Gifts, Nov. 14, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Frank D. Madison elected Trustee; Gift from Mrs. H. St. Goar of land in Placer County; R. L. Wilbur granted leave of absence, Swain acting president, Dec 19, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - [no subjects], Feb 13, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - John T. Nourse reelected Trustee, Mar 6, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Cancellation of all earthquake insurance insurance except on hospital, Mar 20, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - [no subjects], Apr 10, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - [no subjects], May 15, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lease to Stanford Home for Convalescent Children renewed, 1930 Jun 12 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Property condemned for widening of the highway, Univ. reimbursed at $3,000 per acre, 1930 Jul 10 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Leland Cutler reelected Trustee; M. C. Sloss reelected Trustee, 1930 Jul 10 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Frank B. Anderson elected trustee; C. O. G. Miller elected trustee; Los Altos - Univ. Road: agreement between S. U. and Santa Clara County; North Bay Farms Co. stock, Aug 14, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Dr. Wilbur re his leave of absence, Oct 23, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Grant from Rockefeller Foundation to medical school for Fluid Research Fund, Dec 11, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Gifts, Jan 15, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Gifts, Feb 13, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Caltex Co. stock; Amendment to Section 1 of Chap. 6 of the By-Laws, Mar 19, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Financing of new Palo Alto Hospital. Stanford University asked to finance equipment; Amendment to Section 1 of Chap. 6 of By-Laws; Fees for basketball pavillion increased, Apr 16, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Revised Articles of Organization of the faculty of the medical school; Carnegie Corporation endowment for Food Research Institute, 1931 May 21 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Bequest, 1931 May 28 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Margaret Byrne professorship in history established, 1931 Jun 18 (Box 19, Folder 18)